Oh, Jesus.
Tanrım.
It can't be done.
Olacak iş değil.
You sure about that?
Emin misin?
Ah. There's a trick, huh?
Hilesi var değil mi?
There's got to be.
Olması gerek.
This guy wouldn't be putting any money on it
İşin içinde hile yoksa...
unless there's a trick, huh?
...bu adam para koymazdı.
I'm telling you... it can't be done.
Söylüyorum... Olacak iş değil.
So you give up?
Yani pes mi ediyorsunuz?
Yeah, all right.
Evet tamam.
Wait. What?
Yok artık. Ne?
No way!
Mümkün değil!
Show me that again.
Bir daha göster.
Sure. You got another $20?
Tabii. Başka 20'liğiniz var mı?
Screw this.
Siktir et.
Ah, don't go away mad.
Ufak tefek şeylere kızıp gitmeyin.
Oh, hey, guys, you want to buy a Rolex?
Gençler Rolex almak ister misiniz?
Whoa, whoa. Hold on.
Dur.
How much for that cheap piece of crap?
O dandik hurdaya ne kadar istiyorsun?
- Look what the wind blew in. - Hey, Merna.
- Bak rüzgar ne getirmiş. - Selam Merna.
Holy crap.
Ha siktir.
Jimmy, my man, I said you would beat the rap.
Jimmy, dostum cezadan sıvışacağını biliyordum.
Hey, Merna, set him up, would you?
Merna, içki gönder hadi.
Merna, no, thanks. I'm good.
Merna, hayır sağ ol. İyiyim.
No, go on. He don't mean it.
Doldur doldur. Laf olsun diye söylüyor.
You just got out of jail. Come on.
Daha yeni hapisten çıktın. Hadi.
You're... you're not gonna have a drink?
Bir içki almayacak mısın?
That'll be the day, huh?
Gün bugündür.
Marco, settle down, okay? I'm in a rush.
Marco sakinleş. Acelem var.
My brother's outside in a taxi. The meter's running.
Abim dışarda, takside. Taksimetre yazıyor.
What... Chuck's outside?
Chuck dışarda mı?
Tell him to pull that broomstick out of his ass
Ona söyle o sopayı götünden çıkarıp...
and get in here. I'm buying.
...buraya gelsin. Ben ısmarlıyorum.
No. No, no, we got no time. We're catching a plane.
Hayır hayır. Vaktimiz yok. Uçağa yetişmemiz lazım.
I came here to say goodbye.
Veda etmeye geldim.
I'm moving to Albuquerque, New Mexico.
Albuquerque, New Mexico'ya taşınıyorum.
Mexico? You skipped bail?
Meksika mı? Mahkemeden mi kaçıyorsun?
New Mexico...
New Mexico...
You know, like, uh, Bugs Bunny and the Road Runner, you know?
Bugs Bunny ve Road Runner gibi.
Yeah. What are you gonna do there?
Ne yapacaksın orda?
I'm gonna work at his law firm, like, in the mailroom.
Onun hukuk firmasında çalışacağım. Posta odasında.
It's a start, anyways.
Başlangıç olur en azından.
What? N-now you're talking crazy, man.
Ne? İşte şimdi saçmalıyorsun dostum.
You just got out of jail. Now you want to go back?
Daha yeni hapisten çıktın. Şimdi de geri dönmek mi istiyorsun?
Because working for him... That's all that is.
Çünkü onun için çalışmak... Bu olur.
Marco... I was done.
Marco... Cezam bitti.
You understand? I didn't beat the rap.
Anlıyor musun? Sıvışmadım.
Chuck flew in and saved my ass.
Chuck geldi ve götümü kurtardı.
It's time to make some changes.
Bazı değişiklikler yapmanın vakti geldi.
Hey, listen, man. You're slippin' Jimmy.
Dinle dosyum sen üç kağıtçı Jimmy'sin.
What do you got to change, huh?
Değiştirecek neyin var?
Everything. It's time to grow up.
Her şeyim. Artık büyüme zamanı.
Yeah, according to who... Chuck?
Evet kime göre? Chuck'a mı?
The same goes for you, man.
Senin için de aynısı geçerli dostum.
You want to spend the rest of your life on that stool?
Hayatının geri kalanını o taburede mi geçirmek istiyorsun?
I mean, come on, Marco. Look at yourself.
Hadi ama Marco. Kendine bir bak.
All right, that's him. I got to hit it.
Bu o. Gitmem gerek.
Geez. His master's voice.
Efendisinin sesi geldi.
Really? Look, come on. Go outside.
- Gerçekten mi? - Hadi ama dışarı çık...
Tell Chuckles that you... you got some business you forgot.
...Chuckles'a unuttuğun bir işin olduğunu söyle.
- Marco. - Come on.
- Marco. - Hadi.
Y... you got to have one last blowout.
Son bir vurgununun olması gerek.
We'll do the watch thing again,
Yine saat olayını yaparız...
but... but maybe we'll pull that, uh...
...belki o asfaltta para...
That tar-money scam you were talking about,
...numarasını çekeriz hani şu anlattığın...
- get some girls... - I made a promise.
- ...birkaç kız buluruz. - Söz verdim.
Yeah, you made a promise, but it was...
Evet söz verdin ama...
W... Whaddyamacallit? Under duress.
...ne zımbırtıysa işte... baskı altındaydın.
Look, he got you out of jail, okay?
Bak, tamam seni hapisten çıkardı.
But he's your brother. I mean, what else is he gonna do?
Ama o senin abin. Ne yapacaktı zaten?
Marco, listen to me, all right?
Marco beni dinle tamam mı?
Chuck's not making me do this.
Bunu bana Chuck yaptırmıyor.
He's giving me an opportunity, and I'm grabbing it.
O bana bir fırsat sunuyor ben de değerlendiriyorum.
Geez, it's like watching Miles Davis give up the trumpet.
Bu Miles Davis'in trompeti bırakışını izmelek gibi.
What? What does that even mean?
Ne? O ne demek oluyor şimdi?
It's just a waste, is all I'm saying.
Kayıp diyorum sadece.
All right, look. I'm gonna fly out there.
Tamam bak oraya uçacağım.
I'm gonna get settled, and I'll call you. Yeah?
Yerleşeceğim. Sonra seni ararım.
All right, Jimmy.
Tamam Jimmy.
Hey, have a safe flight, all right?!
İyi yolculuklar.
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk www.addic7ed.com
- çeviri: Aylin Ergenç -
- Hey.
- Selam.
What's up?
Naber?
Just waiting to talk to Howard.
Howard'la konuşmak için bekliyorum.
Can I ask about what?
Ne hakkında olduğunu sorabilir miyim?
I'm taking your advice.
Tavsiyeni dinliyorum.
I'm, uh, giving the case to HHM.
Dosyayı HHM'e veriyorum.
Why?
Neden?
The fact that Chuck doesn't want me here
Chuck'ın beni burada istemiyor...
has something to do with it.
...oluşunun bunla bir ilgisi var.
I'm so sorry.
Çok üzgünüm.
Why didn't you just tell me?
Neden bana söylemedin?
I just...
Ben sadece...
I didn't want you hating your own brother.
Öz abinden nefret etmeni istemedim.
How did you find out?
Nasıl öğrendin?
Did Kim tell you?
Kim mi söyledi?
I figured it out on my own.
Kendi başıma öğrendim.
It's about time, right?
Zamanı gelmişti değil mi?
I brought the sandpiper stuff with me.
Sandpiper ıvır zıvırını yanımda getirdim.
It's down in my car.
Aşağıda arabada.
I figure your guys could do the outreach.
Gerisini siz halledebilirsiniz diye düşündüm.
If any of those geezers don't want to sign with you,
Eğer o pinponlardan sizinle anlaşmak istemeyen olursa...
just give me their names.
...bana isimlerini verin.
I'll talk them into it.
İkna ederim.
You know, Jimmy, I never wanted it to go this way.
Jimmy, bu şekilde olmasını hiç istemezdim.
If it had been up to me, we would have at least...
Bana kalsaydı en azından-
Howard, I get it.
Howard anlıyorum.
Your brother's very important to the firm.
Abin firma için çok önemli.
Sorry I called you a pig fucker.
Sana domuz sikici dediğim için özür dilerim.
Well...
Yani...
We owe you some money, don't we?
Sana biraz borcumuz var değil mi?
The of-counsel fee... I think we discussed $20,000.
Dışardan anlaşma ücreti... Sanırım 20000 dolar demiştik.
That and whatever the common-fund proceeds
O ve ortak fona Sandpiper...
of sandpiper ultimately adds up to,
...ne katkı sağlarsa gelirin...
you'll receive 20% of that...
...%20'si senin olacak.
Should be a very nice payday for you when it comes.
Günü geldiğinde senin için iyi bir ödeme olmalı.
Yep.
Evet.
I've got something for you, too.
Ben de sana bir şey getirdim.
Uh, it's a shopping list for Chuck.
Chuck için alışveriş listesi.
I mean, he's doing better,
Daha iyiye gidiyor...
but he still needs deliveries every day.
...yine de her gün teslimat gerekiyor.
I think he'd be more comfortable with someone else doing it.
Başkası yaparsa o daha rahat olur diye düşünüyorum.
I see.
Anlıyorum.
You don't have to do it personally.
Bizzat yapmana gerek yok.
It just needs to get done.
Sadece yapılmalı.
It's pretty straightforward.
Baya net aslında.
The ice is a pain in the ass, but he needs it.
Buz tam bir baş ağrısı, ama ona lazım.
I usually sneak into a motel and fill a garbage bag,
Genelde bir motele gizlice girip çöp poşetine dolduruyordum...
but you can have whoever you hire just buy it.
...ama sen işi kime verirsen artık ona satın aldırabilirsin.
The most important thing is the newspapers.
En önemlisi gazeteler.
Uh, The New York Times, The Wall Street Journal...
New York Times, Wall Street Journal...
They're a must.
Onlar kesin olmalı.
There's a newsstand on Eubank
Eubank bir gazeteci var...
that has both of them at 6:00 A.M.,
...orda sabah 6'da ikisi de oluyor...
which is good 'cause he's an early riser.
...bu iyi çünkü erken uyanır.
The Albuquerque Journal he gets delivered,
Albuquerque Gazetesi eve geliyor...
but somebody still has to bring it in for him.
...ama yine de birinin dışardan alması gerekli.
You've been doing all of this every day...
Bunların hepsini her gün yapıyor muydun...
For over a year?
...bir seneden fazladır?
You'll take care of this?
Halleder misin?
Absolutely.
Kesinlikle.
I'll get it done and done right.
Düzgün bir şekilde halledeceğim.
I always liked you, Jimmy.
Seni hep sevdim Jimmy.
Remember?
Hatırlar mısın?
I used to call you "Charlie Hustle."
Sana Charlie Hustle derdim.
Yeah, I remember that.
Evet hatırlıyorum.
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
Sana bağırdığım için özür dilerim.
That was nice.
Bu güzeldi.
You sure you're all right?
İyi olduğuna emin misin?
It's not a crime to let it out.
İçini dökmek suç değil.
There's nothing to let out. Chuck's a sick man.
Dökecek bir şey yok. Chuck hasta bir adam.
That's no excuse.
Bu bahane değil.
He's my brother.
O benim abim.
He thinks I'm a scumbag.
Pislik olduğumu düşünüyor.
There's nothing I can do to change that.
Bunu değiştirmek için yapabileceği bir şey yok.
What else is there to say?
Başka söylenecek ne var?
Wow. That's mature.
Çok olgunca.
Dalai Lama's got nothing on me.
Dalai Lama yanımda halt etmiş.
O-64, as in, "oh, to be 64 again!"
O-64 "oh, keşke yine 64 olsam!"
O-64.
O-64.
All right. Next up... We got... N-32.
Ve sırada... N-32.
"N" as in "Nancy... Reagan," a first lady with a lot of style.
N  "Nancy Reagan" stil sahibi bir first lady.
Anybody else seen "Hellcats of the Navy"?
Hellcats of the Navy filmini izleyen var mı?
All right. No winners yet?
Tamamdır. Hala kazanan yok mu?
Okay, here's... B-2, just like the B-2 bomber,
İşte B-2, aynen B-2 bombacısı gibi...
the stealth...
...gizlice.
There's probably one taking off over at Kirtland right now.
Şu an muhtemelen Kirtland'in üzerinden gidiyordur.
We would never know because it's stealthy.
Ama bilemeyiz çünkü gizlice oluyor.
Still no winners? No?
Hala kazanan yok mu?
Here we have...
İşte şimdi...
B-4, another "B." How about that?
B-4. Yine B harfi. Buna ne demeli?
As in, "before too long, we're gonna have another winner."
"Birazdan yeni bir kazanananımız olacak"taki gibi.
No? Nobody? Okay.
Yok mu? Hiç kimse? Peki.
All right.
Tamam.
And here comes...
İşte geliyor...
Hey, it's our old friend "B."
Eski dostunuz B tekrar.
B-12.
B-12.
"B," as in, uh...
Şeydeki B...
"Betrayal"...
İhanetteki...
Benedict Arnold betrayed The United States.
Benedict Arnold'ın Birleşik Devletlere ihanet etmesindeki B.
Still no winners.
Hala kazanan yok.
No?
Yok mu?
Okay.
Tamam.
Here it is.
İşte geliyor.
Oh, what are the odds?
Bunun ihtimali nedir ki?
Four B's in a row. That's...
Üst üste dört B.
B-7.
B-7.
"B" as in...
Şeydeki B...
"B" as in..."Brother"... brother.
Abi'deki B.
B-7... "Seven brides for seven brothers."
B-7 "Yedi abi için yedi gelin."
I'm sure a lot of you have brothers.
Eminim çoğunuzun abisi vardır.
It's not like mine, though.
Benimki gibi değildir yine de...
Any winners yet?
Henüz kazanan yok mu?
Take a... take another look, okay?
Bir daha bakın tamam mı?
I'll wait.
Bekliyorum.
All I'm gonna say is,
Diyeceğim o ki...
if it's another "B," could have a real problem here.
...yine B çıkarsa bir problem olabilir.
And...
Ve...
Hey, it is another "B."
Ve işte bir başka B.
B-5, as in,
B-5...
"boy, this 'B' thing is really starting to tick me off."
" Bu B olayı beni iyice gıcık etmeye başladı" daki B.
"B" as in "battleship." "B" as in "bourbon."
Barakanın B'si, burbonun B'si...
"B" as in "Belize"... Beautiful place, so I've heard.
Belize'in B'si. Duyduğuma göre çok güzel bir yermiş.
I would love to go there.
Oraya gitmek isterdim.
But, uh, let's face it... That's never gonna happen.
Ama kabul edelim... Bu hiç olmayacak.
None of us is ever leaving this godforsaken wasteland.
Hiçbirimiz bu kahrolası çolak araziden çıkamayacağız.
Sorry.
Afedersiniz.
Scratch that. Moving on.
Bunu silin. Devam ediyoruz.
I mean, what is it with this place?
Buranın olayı ne?
It's... it's like living inside an easy-bake oven.
Hızlı pişiren fırının içinde yaşamak gibi.
I mean, look out that window.
Yani şu camdan dışarı bakın.
It's... it's like a soulless,
Ruhsuz...
radioactive Georgia O’Keeffe hellscape out there,
...radyoaktif Georgia O’Keeffe cehennemi gibi dışarısı...
crawling with coral snakes and scorpions and...
...mercan yılanları ve akreplerin kol gezdiği...
You ever see the movie "The Hills Have Eyes"?
Hills Have Eyes filmini izlediniz mi?
It's a documentary!
Bir belgesel!
God forbid your car breaks down...
Tanrı korusun arabanız bozulur da...
You have to walk 10 steps.
...10 adım yürümek zorunda kalırsanız...
You got a melanoma the size of a pineapple
...ananas kadar bir tümörünüz oluyor...
where your head used to be.
...kafanızın olması gereken yerde.
And so you ask, "why?" Why?
Siz de soruyorsunuz "Neden?"
If... if that's how I feel, why do I live here?
Böyle hissediyorsam neden burda yaşıyorum?
Why?!
Neden?
Excuse me.
Afedersiniz.
Are you gonna read that number?
Numarayı okuyacak mısınız?
Yeah. I'm gonna read your number.
Evet. Numaranızı okuyacağım.
And it's another "B."
Ve bir başka B.
It's another frigging "B." Boy, of course.
Bir başka lanet B. Tabii ki.
Why not? Why not?!
Neden olmasın? Neden olmasın ki?
And the next number...
Ve sıradaki numara...
Uh, quick question...
Bir şey soracağım...
Who here knows what a Chicago sunroof is?
Chicago tepe penceresinin ne olduğunu bilen var mı?
Anybody?
Hiçkimse?
You, sir? No? Okay.
Siz efendim? Hayır mı? Peki.
True story... uh, back home, uh, there was this guy named Chet.
Gerçek hikaye: geldiğim yerde Chet adlı bir adam vardı.
Now, Chet was a real asshole.
Chet tam bir göt oğlanıydı.
He might have owed me some money.
Bana biraz borcu olabilir.
He might have slept with my wife...
Karımla yatmış olabilir...
Before she became my ex-wife.
Kendisi eski karım olmadan önce.
The details don't matter.
Detayların önemi yok.
Suffice it to say, I was wronged.
Şunu söylemek yeterli olur: haksızlığa uğradım.
All right, so, one summer evening,
Bir yaz akşamı...
I was out having a few drinks... One or two, maybe three.
...dışarda bir şeyler içiyordum. Bir, iki belki üç...
You get the picture?
Anlıyor musunuz?
And, uh, who do I see? Chet.
Kimi göreyim? Chet.
He drove up, and he double-parked
Geldi ve marketin önüne iki sıra...
outside a dairy queen and went in to get some soft-serve.
...kaplayacak şekilde park edip yumuşak dondurma için içeri girdi.
Now, Chet drove... And this will give you an idea
Chet'in kullandığı... Bu size bir fikir verir...
of exactly what kind of a douchebag this guy was...
...tabi ki onun gibi her magandanın kullandığı cinsten...
Drove a white pearlescent BMW 7 series
...sedefli beyaz BMW 7 serisiydi.
with white leather interior.
Beyaz iç döşemeli.
So, I saw that thing,
O şeyi gördüm ve...
and I had... I'd had a few, like I said.
...dediğim gibi biraz demlenmiştim.
And, uh... I climbed up top,
Üstüne çıktım ve...
and I may have...
...belki biraz...
Defecated, uh, through the sunroof.
...tepe penceresinden içeri dışkılamış olabilirim.
Not my finest hour... I'll grant you that.
En iyi zamanım değildi. Bunu söyleyebilirim.
But that's what a Chicago sunroof is.
Ama Chicago tepe penceresi budur.
Now you know. It's a real thing.
Artık biliyorsunuz. Bu gerçek bir şey.
I didn't make it up. I'm not the first person to do it.
Ben uydurmadım. Yapan ilk kişi değilim.
There's a name for it.
Bir adı var.
Guy wanted some soft-serve... I gave him some soft-serve.
Adam yumuşak dondurma istiyordu, ben de biraz verdim.
I did not know that his children were in the backseat.
Çocuklarının arka koltukta oturmakta olduğunu bilmiyordum.
There was a level of tint on the windows
Camlara film çekilmişti...
that I'll maintain to this day
...belirtmek isterim ki bugün...
was not legal in an Illinois-licensed vehicle.
...Illinois plakalı araçlarda kullanımı yasaktır.
But somehow, that's on me, I guess.
Ama bir şekilde, bu benim suçum sanırım.
Who leaves two cub scouts in a double-parked car
Kim iki çocuğu ikili park edilmiş, motoru...
with the engine running?!
...çalışan br arabanın içinde bırakır?
Come on.
Hadi ama.
Now, Chet was connected, see?
Şimdi Chet'e bağladık.
Like, uh, Cicero connected.
Cicero'nun bağlanışı gibi.
So, usually, I'd be looking at malicious mischief,
Yani karşımda kasten hasar verme...
public intoxication, disorderly conduct, maybe,
...çevre kirliliği, ahlaka aykırı davranış, belki de...
but he's got the D.A. saying indecent exposure,
...savcıyı teşhir olduğuna ikna etti ki...
calling me a sex offender. What?
...cinsel suçlu olayım. Ne?
One little Chicago sunroof, and suddenly I'm Charles Manson?!
Küçük bir Chicago tepe penceresi ve birden Charles Manson mıyım?
And that's where it all went off the rails.
İşler böylece raydan çıktı.
I've been paying for it ever since.
O günden beri de bedel ödüyorum.
That's why I'm here!
O yüzden buradayım!
I don't...
Ben...
You know what?
Ne var biliyor musunuz?
Any of this stuff you want, come get it.
Gelip şunların hangisini istiyorsanız alın.
Kitty-cat notebooks for everybody.
Herkese kedicikli defter.
- What can I get you? - Old style.
- Ne vereyim? - Eski tarz.
Make it two.
İki olsun.
You got it.
Tamamdır.
- What happened to Merna? - Merna?
- Merna'ya ne oldu? - Merna mı?
She's doing all right.
İyidir.
She's my step-mom.
Benim üvey annem.
She don't come in much anymore.
Pek gelmiyor artık.
Tell her slippin' Jimmy says hello.
Üç kağıtçı Jimmy selam söyledi dersin.
- Slippin' Jimmy? - Yeah, she'll know.
- Üç kağıtçı Jimmy mi? - Evet, o anlar.
I'll tell her. That'll be $5.50.
Söylerim 5,5 ediyor.
Marco...
Marco...
You gorgeous hunk of a man...
Seni harika insan yarması...
How long will you keep me waiting?
Beni daha ne kadar bekleteceksin?
Mnh! Wake up, you fat son of a bitch.
Uyan lan şişko piç.
Bought you a beer.
Sana bira aldım.
- Jimmy? - In the flesh.
- Jimmy? - Ta kendisi.
Hey.
Selam.
So, I'm not dark enough for you, huh?
Yani senin için yeterince koyu tenli değil miyim?
No, no. I'm just saying I don't see any color.
Hayır hayır, sadece diyorum ki renk değişimi göremiyorum.
I mean, 10 years in the desert, you should look like, uh,
10 seneyi çölde geçirdin, şey gibi görünmeliydin...
Anthony Quinn in "Lawrence of Arabia."
...Lawrence of Arabia'daki Anthony Quinn gibi.
Turks... They paid me a golden treasure!
Türkler... Bana altın madeni sundular.
- Yet I am poor... - Because I am a...
- Hala fakirim... - Çünkü ben...
- River to my people!
- Halkım için bir nehirim!
Well, hey, I'm Irish, okay?
Ben İrlandalıyım tamam mı?
I spend my time staying out of the sun.
Vaktimi güneşten uzak durarak geçiririm.
Speaking of pale sons of bitches,
Soluk orospu çocuklarından bahsetmişken...
how's your brother doing?
...abin nasıl?
Chuck's fine.
Chuck iyi.
Still working for him?
Hala onun için mi çalışıyorsun?
Sometimes.
Ara sıra..
What about you... I mean, besides falling asleep on a bar
Ya sen... Yani çarşamba öğlen 4'te...
at 4:00 on a Wednesday afternoon?
...barda uyuyakalmak dışında?
"Lake Michigan Standpipe"?
Lake Michigan Yangın Borusu?
- What's that? - My brother-in-law
- O da ne? - Kayın birader...
owns the company.
...şirketin sahibi.
Wait. Hold it. You got married?
Bekle. Nasıl yani, evlendin mi?
No, no, no. My... my... My sister Angie's husband.
Hayır hayır kardeşim Angie'nin kocası.
So, what the hell's a standpipe?
Yangın borusu ne be?
Standpipe... You know what a standpipe is.
Yangın borusu işte bildiğin.
- I don't think so. - Fire department comes.
- Sanmıyorum. - İtfaiyeciler geliyor.
They stick one end of the hose on the hydrant.
Bir ucunu musluk ağzında takıyorlar...
The other end goes on the standpipe.
...diğer taraf da yangın borusuna gidiyor.
The water goes out the standpipe,
Su yangın borusundan...
through the sprinklers, and then douses the flames.
...çise şeklinde çıkıyor ve alevlere gidiyor.
It's important stuff.
Önemli bir şey.
So, that's what a standpipe is, huh?
Yani yangın borusu bu demek?
Well, it's a dry standpipe. There's also the wet standpipe.
Bu kuru yangın borusu. Bir de ıslağı var.
What's the difference?
Ne farkı var?
I don't know I-if I could explain it to a layman.
Bilmeyen birine anlatamam sanırım.
Excuse me. How's your mom?
Afedersin.
Oh, she passed away about three years ago.
Üç sene kadar önce vefat etti.
Ah. That's too bad. She was a great lady.
Çok çok kötü. İyi bir hanımdı.
Yeah. From Wisconsin, right?
Wisconsin'liydi değil mi?
- Yeah. - The funeral out there?
- Evet. - Cenaze orda mıydı?
No, it was... Here.
Hayır, burdaydı.
Here?
Burada mı?
Yeah, well, we were only in town for a few days, so...
Sadece birkaç günlüğüne gelmiştik...
You were in town. You didn't look me up?
Buraya geldin ve beni aramadın mı?
Chuck was in the middle of a big case,
Chuck'ın önemli bir davası vardı...
and, uh, we couldn't stay around, so...
...fazla uzun kalamadı...
Can I get you guys anything else?
Beyler başka bir şey vereyim mi?
I'm good. You want anything?
Ben istemem. Sen bir şey ister misin?
Nah. Your change here, too.
Para üstünüz burda.
Uh, yeah, okay. Hey.
Teşekkürler.
Thank you.
Sağ ol.
How's my cutlass running?
Benim araba nasıl?
Gets me around.
İdare ediyor.
Well, it's a classic.
O klasiktir.
Little bodywork, paint job... Really be something.
Biraz tadilat ve boyayla, güzel bir şeyler olabilir.
So, what you gonna do while you're here?
Buralardayken ne yapacaksın şimdi?
I don't know.
Bilmiyorum.
See the sights, you know,
Manzaraya bakarım...
catch a Cubbies game from the bleachers,
...beleş tepeden Cubbies maçı izlerim...
get a hot dog at Henry's.
...Henry's'den sosisli alırım.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Evet.
Correct.
Doğru.
I'm gonna see them tomorrow.
Onları yarın göreceğim.
Yeah, both of them.
Evet, ikisini de.
Is he a regular?
Sık gelir mi?
No.
Hayır.
You're buying, I'm selling.
Sen alıyorsun, ben satıyorum.
All right, then.
Tamam o zaman.
All I'm asking is that you take a look.
Tek istediğim bir göz atman.
I'm sorry, buddy... no offense.
Üzgünüm dostum, alınma.
I'm just... you know, I'm not interested.
Sadece ilgilenmiyorum işte.
Come on, man.
Hadi ama.
What's it gonna hurt to take a look?
Bir bakmaktan ne çıkar?
It'll take you two seconds.
İki saniyeni alır.
All right.
Tamam.
All right. Show me what you got.
Göster bakalım ne varmış.
Okay.
Pekii.
Do you see it?
Gördün mü?
I see a Kennedy half-dollar.
Ben bir Kennedy yarım doları görüyorum.
Which way is he facing?
Ne tarafa dönük?
JFK's facing left.
JFK sola dönük.
Exactly.
Aynen.
Hey, which way is he supposed to be facing?
Ne tarafa dönük olmalıydı?
Right... he's supposed to be facing right.
Sağ. Sağ tarafa bakıyor olmalıydı.
Okay, so why... Why is this one facing left?
Tamam. Neden bu sola bakıyor?
November 22, 1963... Kennedy is assassinated, right?
22 Kasım 1963'de Kennedy sukiaste uğradı değil mi?
The whole nation goes into mourning.
Tüm ulus yasa boğuldu.
They start naming everything in sight after him.
Her şeye onun adını vermeye başladılar.
And the mint wants in on the act.
Para basımı da devreye girdi.
So, in '64, they decide to change the Lincoln half-dollar
64'te Lincoln yarım doları...
into the Kennedy half-dollar.
...Kennedy'ye çevirmeye karar verdiler.
When they design it, they put Kennedy facing right,
Tasarlarken Kennedy'yi sağa baktırdılar...
facing east, just the way they had Lincoln.
...doğuya doğru Lincoln'de olduğu gibi.
- You know why? - Mnh-mnh.
Neden biliyor musun?
He symbolizes the dawn.
Gün doğumunu temsil ediyordu.
It's why pretty much every grave everywhere faces east, you know?
Aşağı yukarı bu yüzden her mezar taşı, fotograflar hep doğuya bakar.
So the spirit of the dead person faces the rising sun.
Ölü insanın yüzü doğan düneşe baksın diye.
You know, it's a death thing. It's a burial thing.
Bu bir ölüm meselesi. Vefat meselesi.
But there's one technician in the Denver mint, right?
Ama Denver para basımında bir tekniker vardı.
And this guy... he believed in, uh, the new frontier...
Bu adam yeni sınırlara inanırdı...
Camelot, the whole deal.
...Camelot meselesi gibi.
So, the assassination just destroyed him.
Suikast onu mahvetti.
When he sees that coin with Kennedy facing east,
Kennedy'nin doğuya baktığı bozukluğu gördükçe...
facing the American past, pissed him off.
...Amerika'nın geçmişine baktıkça kızıyordu.
And so he went rogue.
O da bir düzen yaptı.
Without telling anybody,
Kimseye söylemeden...
he flipped things around so that Kennedy was facing west,
...işleri tersine çevirdi ve Kennedy batıya bakıyordu...
towards the new frontier, the future.
...yeni sınırlara, geleceğe.
Now, the mint struck about 3,000 of these
Para 3000 tane falan basıldı...
before they figured it out.
...onlar durumu fark etmeden.
They canned the guy.
Adamı paketlediler.
About 1,000 of them made it out into general circulation.
1000 tane kadarı piyasaya sürülmüş oldu.
They managed to get most of them back,
Çoğunu geri almayı başardılar...
melt them down, but...
...erittiler fakat...
There are still...
Hala...
200-plus floating around out there.
...200 küsur tanesi ortalıkta dolanıyor.
What's that? I didn't catch that.
Ne dedin? Yakalayamadım.
I didn't say anything.
Bir şey demedim.
Do you mind, buddy?
Müsade eder misin?
We're having a private conversation here.
Özel bir konuşma yapıyoruz.
This one's not in perfect condition,
Bu harika konumda değil...
but on the open market,
...ama piyasada...
I'd say it's worth... 600 or 800 bucks.
...600- 800 dolara gider.
$800?
800 dolar mı?
Yeah, but I'm hard up,
Evet ama ben biraz sıkışığım...
so I'll take, uh, $100 for it.
...sana 100'e bırakırım.
You want me to give you $100 for a half-dollar.
Yarım dolar için sana 100 dolar vermemi mi istiyorsun?
I want you to give me $100 for an $800 coin.
Bana 800 dolar için 100 dolar vermeni istiyorum.
Yeah, I don't know, man. You know?
Bilemiyorum dostum.
I'm gonna go drain the snake. Think about it.
Ben etin suyunu sıkmaya gidiyorum. Sen düşün.
This guy's playing me, right?
Herif benle kafa buluyor değil mi?
Definitely.
Kesinlikle.
Slick son of a bitch.
Kurnaz orospu çocuğu.
You know, I should...
Ne yapmalıyım biliyor musun...
You know what? I know this guy on wabash...
Tanıdığım bir adam var...
Coin dealer, a friend of my uncle's.
...para koleksiyoncusu, arkadaşımın amcası.
Hey, Joey, can I use your phone?
Joey telefonu kullanabilir miyim?
Local call. Keep it short.
- Şehir içi. - Kısa tut.
Right on.
Tamam.
Let's see. Man.
Görelim bakalım.
I'm gonna call this guy, and when he tells me this is a scam,
Bu adamı arayacağım ve bunun numara olduğunu söylerse...
you know what I'm gonna do? I'm gonna call the cops
...ne yapacağım biliyor musun? Polisi arayıp...
and get this scumbag thrown in the can.
...bu pisliği içeri tıktıracağım.
You're my witness, okay?
Tanığımsın tamam mı?
Facing west.
Batıya bakıyormuş.
My hairy ass.
Ay götüm.
Hey. How you doing?
Selam. Nasılsın?
Yeah, it's Alvin, Dave Tanner's nephew.
Ben Alvin, Dave Tanner'ın yeğeni.
Yeah, mm-hmm.
Evet.
Yeah, that's right.
Evet doğru.
Hey, this is gonna sound like the beginning of a bad joke,
Bak bu kötü bir şakanın başlangıcı gibi gelecek ama...
but, uh, I'm in this bar, and I've got this guy
...bir bardayım ve adamın teki...
spinning this cock-and-bull story
...martaval okuyor.
about this, uh, 50-cent piece he's trying to sell me.
Bana bir 50 sent satmaya çalışıyor.
He says, uh... Says Kennedy's supposed to be
Kennedy'nin batıya bakması...
facing west or something.
...gerektiğini falan söylüyor.
Yeah?
Öyle mi?
Yeah.
Evet.
Yeah. That's what he said... Denver.
Evet öyle dedi... Denver.
Jesus. No kidding?
Dalga mı geçiyorsunuz?
- At the tone... - Well, listen, I got to go.
Bakın kapatmam gerek.
All right? Uh, thank you.
Tamam mı? Teşekkür ederim.
And I owe you one.
Size borçluyum.
Thanks, Joey.
Sağ ol Joey.
So, what did he say?
Ne dedi?
Yeah, you know, he... He didn't really know much.
Pek bilmiyormuş ya.
I'll tell you what... I'll give you $50 for it.
Bak ne diyeceğim 50 dolar veririm.
$50? I'm taking a bath at $100.
50 mi ben yüzlüğün üstünde yıkanıyorum be.
All right. Okay.
Tamam tamam.
Look, I got... $64 right here.
Bak burda 64 dolarım var.
It's an $800 coin, okay?
Bu 800 dolarlık bir bozukluk tamam mı?
I'm not gonna sell it to you for $64.
Sana 64 dolara satmıyorum.
Okay, if you wait for me, I'll get you 100 bucks.
Tamam eğer beklersen 100 dolarını getiririm.
- I don't know. - Okay.
- Bilmiyorum. - Tamam.
Hey, buddy, I got 75 bucks right here.
Dostum burda 75 dolarım var.
I... I... sorry. I need $100.
Kusura bakmayın 100 lazım.
Hey, slick, nobody's talking to you.
Bu seni ilgilendirmiyor çakal.
Mind your own business, okay?
Kendi işine bak tamam mı?
- Come on. - Cash money... $80.
- Hadi ama. - Nakit para, 80 dolar.
Look, if you give me a chance, I'll be back with $110.
Bak bana şans verirsen 110 dolarla burda olurum.
How long will that be? I don't know.
- Ne kadar sürer? - Bilmiyorum.
I got to catch a train, come back...
Bilmiyorum treni yakalayıp dönmeliyim...
- Hour, hour and a half at the most. - Yeah, you know, this guy
- Bir saat bilemedin bir buçuk... - Bu adam senin için...
- was getting ready to call the cops on you. - No, I was not.
- ...polis çağıracaktı nerdeyse. - Hayır çağırmayacaktım.
What? Why would you do that? That...
Neden? Bunu neden yapasın?
Now this guy is making shit up!
Götünden atıyor.
Hey, I got $110 right here. That's...
Bak burda 110 dolarım var.
- Sold. - No! No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Satıldı. - Hayır! Hayır hayır hayır hayır.
This guy's got the cash. Now...
Adam nakit verdi.
- Don't do that. - Here, take care of that.
- Yapma bunu. - Al, iyi bak ona.
That's history right there.
Tarih yatıyor.
- Hey, you can't do that. - Hey, money talks.
- Bunu yapamazsın. - Hey para konuşur.
You lost. It's over.
Kaybettin. Bitti.
No, it's not over. No, that's crap.
Hayır bitmedi. Bu çok saçma.
And where do you think you're going, huh?
Nereye gittiğini sanıyorsun?
Hey, back off, dude.
Geri çekil dostum.
Yeah, I'll back off when you give me the JFK back.
Sen JFK'yi verdiğinde geri çekilirim.
Hey, Joey, call the cops.
Joey polisi ara.
This guy just tried to rip me off.
Bu adam beni dolandırdı.
Hey, this guy's a liar. I did not rip anybody off.
O adam yalancı. Kimseyi dolandırmadım.
Yes, you did!
Evet öyle yaptın.
You come back in here, and your ass is grass!
Buraya geri gelirsen siki tuttun bil!
I got friends, buddy!
Arkadaşlarım var dostum.
Do you hear me?! You double-dealing bastard!
Beni duyuyor musun? Seni ikili oynayan piç!
I got friends!
Arkadaşlarım var.
You are so beautiful!
Çok güzelsin.
Hey, everybody, next round's on us!
Millet sıradaki içkiler bizden!
All right. Are you listening?
Tamam. Dinliyor musun?
Can you keep a secret?
Sır tutabilir misin?
Yeah. Absolutely.
Evet tabii ki.
Okay, his name is Idi Abbassi.
Adı Idi Abbassi.
He's 27 years old.
27 yaşında.
He's a Nigerian prince, all right?
Nijeryalı bir prens.
He's worth, conservatively, $400 million.
En kötü ihtimalle 400 milyon dolar ederi var.
The dictatorship of equatorial Uqbar Orbis
Ekvator Uqbar Orbis diktatörlüğü...
is detaining him on trumped-up charges.
...onu saçma sapan nedenlerle alıkoyuyor.
Now, the Abbassi family... They're going crazy.
Abbasi ailesi deliye dönmüş durumda.
They will reward whoever helps them get their boy back.
Oğullarına kavuşmalarına yardım edecek herkesi ödüllendirecekler.
The hitch is, the banks have frozen their...
Tek pürüz banka hesaplarını dondurmuş durumda...
Assets... I'm talking Irish sweeps tickets,
İrlanda piyango bileti diyorum...
a whole trunk full of 'em.
...bir bagaj dolusu.
They're just sitting at O'Hare, impounded in customs.
O'Hare'de gümrükte mahsur kalmış durumdalar.
Now, I know what you're saying... "So what?"
"Ne olmuş?" diyeceğini biliyorum...
I can leave this as security, but you got to understand...
Bunu depozito olarak bırakabilirim ama anlamalısınız...
This violin is my livelihood. It's a valuable antique.
...bu keman benim ekmek teknem. Kıymetli bir antikadır.
What do you mean it doesn't belong to you?
Ne demek size ait değil?
I'll pay you 900 bucks for this... cash on the barrel.
Bunun için 900 dolar veririm hemen, nakit.
I don't know. I hate to part with it.
Bilmiyorum. Bir parçası olmaktan nefret ediyorum.
It's been in my family for years.
Yıllardır aileme aitti.
You can keep a secret, right?
Sır tutabilirsin değil mi?
Yeah, absolutely.
Evet kesinlikle.
But the point is, you need a good front,
Önemli nokta dış görünümün iyi olması...
so you're gonna have the most return on your dollars.
...böylece en iyi dönüşü dolarla alıryorsun.
But I know this customs officer...
Tanıdığım bir gümrük memuru var...
That money, then make it an investment.
Bu parayla bir yatırım yap.
If the price is right.
Fiyat düzgünse.
And I'm all about investments, all about what's coming next.
Benim olayım yatırım, sırada neyin olduğu...
Hey, kid, help me get my wife's car
Hey çocuk, karımın arabasını şu kötü...
out of this bad neighborhood.
...mahalleden almama yardım et.
Sir, sir, could you help me?
Bayım yardım edebilir misiniz?
Tell me... are these today's numbers?
Bunlar bugünün şanslı numaraları mı?
Now, none of this was strictly legal,
Bunların hiçbiri kesin olarak yasal değil...
and the import taxes would have been a killer... have at it.
...yani ithalat vergisi canımıza okuyabilir.
So he had to find a way to get the money into the country
Yani bizim de parayı ülkeye kimse fark etmeden...
without anyone knowing about it.
...sokacak bir yol bulmamız gerek.
He coated the cash with this black stuff...
Nakiti bu siyah maddeyle boyadık.
Vectrol paste.
Vectrol paste.
And the only way to get it off is with a special chemical.
Silmenin tek yolu bu özel kimyasal.
It's not cheap, but the upside?
Ucuz değil ama iyi tarafı?
The upside is huge.
İyi tarafı çok büyük.
Can you keep a secret?
Sır tutabilir misin?
You know, the guy in "dances with wolves"?
Kurtlarla Dans'taki adamı biliyor musun?
A guy like you, who's got some money,
Senin gibi bir adam, parası olan...
who's got some money to throw around...
...savuracak paraya sahip...
Now, I know what you're saying... "Who cares?"
"Kim takar?" dediğini biliyorum ama...
No matter which one wins, we're gonna get a piece.
Hangi taraf kazanırsa kazansın biz payımızı alacağız.
He's got a gambling problem.
Kumar problemi var.
Nobody can ever come after you, but you get the profit.
Kimse peşinden gelemez ama sen karlı çıkarsın.
- The price is right. - It's a win-win for you.
- Fiyat doğru. - Senin için kazan-kazan.
It's a lose-lose for everybody else.
Diğer herkes için kaybet-kaybet durumu.
You want to tell the guy you've got a 14.
Sen adama elinde 14 olduğunu söylüyorsun...
He checks...
O kontrol ediyor...
Realizes he's... It's not gonna just be you.
Sadece sende olmadığını anlıyor...
It's gonna be a piece of the pie.
Pastadan bir dilim olacak.
But you're gonna own a full mountain range, guaranteed.
Ama sen tüm paranı alacaksın, garantili.
Can you keep...
Sır...
A secret?
...tutabilir misin?
'Cause I really...
Çünkü bunu cidden...
Really shouldn't...
...bunu cidden...
Shouldn't be telling you this.
...söylememem gerekiyor.
- Hey.
- Merhaba. - Selam.
You are not Kevin Costner.
Kevin Costner değilsin.
I was last night.
Dün gece öyleydim.
Jesus.
Tanrım.
Asshole.
Göt herif.
I mean, seriously?
Cidden mi ya?
Oh, my God.
Tanrım.
- Lucianne?! Lucianne! - What?
- Lucianne?! Lucianne! - Ne?
- He's not Kevin Costner. - What?!
- O Kevin Costner değil.
Well, who's this guy?
Bu kim?
Uh, not Kevin Costner's manager.
Kevin Costner'ın menajeri değil.
Oh, come on. Come on. Let's go.
Hadi hadi gidelim.
Uh, hang on. Got to get my dress on.
Elbisemi alayım.
Come on. Get the hell out of this dump.
Gidelim bu çöplükten.
So, are you sure he's not a manager?
Onun menajer olmadığına emin misin?
Yes, Luci, I am sure.
Evet Luci, eminim.
But he said he was gonna give me his card.
Ama bana kartını vereceğini söylemişti.
Does this look like a manager's place?
Sence burası bir menajer evi mi gibi görünüyor mu?
- Maybe. - Can I interest you
- Belki. - Birer kokteyl...
ladies in some mimosas?
...ilginizi çeker miydi?
At least stick around long enough to get dressed.
En azından giyinene kadar dursaydınız.
Oh, oh. Screw you.
Siktir git.
If you build it, I will come.
Sen mahal verirsen ben de gelirim.
Lucy, come on.
Lucy hadi.
Okay. Bye.
Tamam. Hoşçakal.
Come on.
Hadi.
That door sticks.
Kapı sıkışır.
Yeah, okay. I got it.
Tamam hallettim.
Okay.
Tamam.
Go. Go.
Çık. Çık.
You have 15 messages.
15 mesajınız var.
This is Greta Muller.
Ben Greta Muller.
I wanted to check to see if my wi...
Vasiyetimi kontrol etmek-
My name's Gary Albert Arnold.
Adım Gary Albert Arnold.
I'd like to discuss making a...
Bir vasiyet hazırlamak-
Hi, Mr. McGill.
Merhaba Bay McGill.
I'm calling on behalf of my mother.
Annem adına arıyorum.
She's in assisted living, and...
Kendisi yaşam destekli bir-
Uh, yes, Mr. McGill, this is Manny Hollinger...Again.
Bay McGill, Ben Manny Hollinger... tekrar...
Uh, I hate to...
Bunu yapmaktan-
So, what's it gonna be today, pal?
Bugün ne yapıyoruz kanka?
I'm up for anything and everything.
Herhangi bir şeye ve her şeye varım.
Marco, I'm sorry. I got to go back.
Marco üzgünüm. Dönmem gerek.
What?
Ne?
Uh, it's be great, and I appreciate your hospitality,
Çok güzel geçti ve misafirperverliğine minnettarım...
but a week's gonna have to do it.
...ama bir hafta yeterliydi.
I got to go home.
Eve dönmem gerek.
I already called in sick.
İşten izin aldım bile.
Come on, man.
Hadi ama dostum.
This is home. Y-you hate it out there.
Evin burası. Ordan nefret ediyorsun.
What do you got to go back to?
Niye geri dönmen gerek ki?
My clients.
Müvekkillerim.
Clients.
Müvekkillermiş.
What... what are you... Like a gigolo or something?
Ne iş yapıyorsun? Jigolo falan mısın?
Uh, Marco...
Marco...
I'm a lawyer.
Avukatım.
What?
Ne?
Honest to God.
Gerçekten.
I do elder law, which is like wills and estates.
Yaşlı hukukuna bakıyorum bu da vasiyet ve mülk oluyor.
So you're ripping off old people?
Yani yaşlıları mı soyuyorsun?
No, I'm not ripping off old people.
Hayır yaşlıları soymuyorum.
I'm not ripping off anybody.
Kimseyi soymuyorum.
Holy crap. Slippin' Jimmy's a lawyer?
Ha siktir! Üç kağıtçı Jimmy avukat mı?
No wonder you want to go back.
Geri dönmek istemene şaşmamalı.
I mean, you got to be king of the desert,
Çölün kralı olmalısın...
driving around town in a white caddy, making bank.
...beyaz bir caddy sürüp servet kazanıyorsundur.
I'm not making bank.
Servet kazanmıyorum.
I'm making a living, more or less.
Geçinecek kadar kazanıyorum, aşağı yukarı.
A living?
Geçinmek mi?
All due respect,
Tüm saygımla...
you're a lawyer and you're not making bank,
...avukatsan ve servet kazanmıyorsan...
you're doing it wrong.
...işini yanlış yapıyorsundur.
Well, I'm building something. Takes time.
Bir şeyler hazırlıyorum. Zaman alıyor.
Well, you're gonna build something, build it out here.
Bir şey hazırlıyorsan burda hazırla.
I mean, lawyers in Chicago make plenty... I assure you.
Chicago'da avukatlar deli gibi kazanıyor emin olabilirsin.
Yeah, I don't know what to tell you, Marco. I...
Ne söyleyeceğimi bilemiyorum Marco.
Chuck's in Albuquerque.
Chuck Albuquerque'da.
Again, all due respect... Chuck's a stuck-up douchebag.
Yine tüm saygımla... Chuck burnu havada yavşağın teki.
I hate to break it to you, but he doesn't even like you.
Bunu söylemek istemezdim ama senden hoşlanmıyor bile.
He's my brother.
O benim abim.
Okay.
Peki.
I... I get it... family.
Anlıyorum, aile.
You got to go back. But...
Geri dönmen gerek. Ama...
Remember this?
Bunu hatırlıyor musun?
The rolex thing. What...
Rolex olayı.
Whatever happened to the guy who used to sell us those?
Bize bunları satan adama ne oldu?
Jin Kang? He got deported.
Jin Kang mi? Sınır dışı edildi.
This is the last one. I say we go for it.
Bu sonuncusu. Yapalım diyorum.
No. Oh, come on.
Hayır. Hadi ama.
Last time, we did what? $600?
Son sefer ne almıştık? 600 dolar mı?
The hot streak we're on, I bet we break a grand, easy.
Geldiğimiz kıvamla kolayca bin yapabiliriz diyorum.
I could lend you some cash.
Sana para verebilirim.
I don't need the money, Jimmy.
Paraya ihtiyacım yok Jimmy.
I need this.
Buna ihtiyacım var.
Come on.
Hadi.
You say you're happy doing wills or whatever,
O vasiyetleri falan yapmaktan mutlu olduğunu söyledin...
good for you, man, seriously.
...senin için sevindim dostum gerçekten.
But I got to tell you...
Ama söylemeliyim...
Standpipes ain't cutting it for me, man.
...yangın boruları beni kesmiyor dostum.
I got nothing, Jimmy.
Hiçbir şeyim yok Jimmy.
Give me this.
Bana bunu ver
Give me this, man.
Bana bunu ver dostum.
I can't do it.
Yapamam.
Come on. Give me this.
Hadi. Bana bunu ver.
Marco. Give me this.
Bana bunu ver.
Come on. Come on. Buddy, listen to me.
Hadi ama. Hadi dostum beni dinle.
I'm listening. Come on.
Dinlemedeyim. Hadi.
Hey. Just one last time.
Son bir kez.
Come on. I'm not being hypnotized.
Hadi ama. Hipnotize olmuyorum.
No? Okay. Come on, one more time.
Hadi. Son defa.
I can't do it.
Yapamam.
Just one more... one more.
Sadece bir kez. Bir kez.
Hey, listen to me. Just listen to you.
- Dinle. - Dinliyorum.
- Yeah, I'm listening. Come on. - No.
- Hadi ama. - Hayır.
It's got to come from the gut, man.
İçinden gelmeli dostum.
Yeah. Yeah.
- Öyle mi? - Öyle.
Oh, that's crazy.
Bu delilik.
Just like a wolf. Go ahead.
Kurt gibi. Hadi.
No, deeper, deeper.
Hayır derinden, derinden.
Yeah, and you do that right at the moment of,
Ve bunu tam o...
you know, pure joy...
....zevk anında yapıyorsun...
Yeah... And it will escalate it 10...
Ve onu 10 katına...
10 times.
10 katına çıkarıyor.
- There's something... - Hey.
Bir şey var.
- It's prehistoric. - Hey, hey. Look.
- Tarih öncesi. - Hey hey bak.
$50, $200, $400.
50, 200, 400 dolar.
Whose is it? I don't know.
- Kimin? - Bilmiyorum.
There's got to be 1,000 bucks in here.
Burda 1000 dolar falan var.
Somebody must have...
Biri cüzdanını-
Oh, damn.
Lanet olsun.
Is he, uh...
O...?
I don't know.
Bilmiyorum.
Hey, buddy, you with us?
Dostum bizimle misin?
Look, the guy's just had too many.
Eleman belli ki fazla kaçırmış.
I say we move on. You want to split this?
Devam edelim derim. Bölüşelim mi?
Marco, you okay?
Marco iyi misin?
Marco?
Marco mu?
What... do you know this guy?
Bu adamı tanıyor musun?
Hey, call 911.
Ambulans çağır.
I need an ambulance.
Ambulans lazım.
My friend's having a heart attack.
Arkadaşım kalp krizi geçiriyor.
We're in an alley,
Bir aradayız...
uh, southeast of Lasalle and Shermer.
...Lasalle ve Shermer'ın güneydoğusu.
No, I-i don't know.
Hayır, bilmiyorum.
He was like this when I found him.
Bulduğumda böyleydi.
Marco, Marco, you with me?
Marco, Marco benimle misin?
You with me? I screwed up.
- Benimle misin? - İçine sıçtım.
No, you did... you did good, buddy.
Hayır, iyi gittin, iyi yaptın dostum.
Just hold on, all right? They're on their way.
Sadece dayan tamam mı? Geliyorlar.
They'll be here in a minute.
Her an burda olabilirler.
Jimmy, you know what?
Jimmy ne var biliyor musun?
Just s-save your breath, okay?
Nefesini harcama tamam mı?
You're gonna be fine.
İyi olacaksın.
This was the greatest week of my life.
Bu hayatımın en güzel haftasıydı.
Hang in there! Hey!
Dayan.
Hey, wake up, man!
Uyan dostum!
Come on! Marco, buddy!
Hadi Marco!
Help!
Yardım edin!
Anybody!
Kimse yok mu!
Marco!
Marco!
- Hey, Jimmy. - Oh, hey, bud.
- Selam Jimmy. - Selam dostum.
Can I bum one?
Bir tane alabilir miyim?
Is that his?
Bu onun mu?
Yeah. His mom gave it to me.
Evet. Annesi verdi.
Thought it looked familiar.
Tanıdık gelmişti.
I figured I'd wear it today,
Bugün takabilirim dedim...
but I don't know.
...ama bilmiyorum.
I'm not a big ring guy, so...
Pek büyük yüzük adamı değilimdir...
Still. Could be worth a couple of bucks.
Yine de birkaç dolar ederi var.
Better head back.
Dönsem iyi olur.
See you inside.
İçerde görüşürüz.
Hey.
Selam.
Is this Ferris Bueller?
Ferris Bueller mı?
Speaking.
Benim.
I don't want to interrupt your big day off.
Büyük boş gününü bölmek istemezdim ama...
Just checking in. What are you up to?
Bir arayayım dedim. Neler yapıyorsun?
You know, burning down the place.
Bilirsin, buraları ateşe veriyorum falan.
I wouldn't expect any less.
Daha azını beklemezdim.
So, whatever it was, did you get it out of your system?
Ee içindeki her neydiyse atıp rahatlayabildin mi?
Yep, all gone.
Evet, bitti gitti.
Good. I want to run something by you.
Güzel. Bir şeyi senin yürütmeni istiyorum.
The sandpiper case... It's getting too big for hhm.
Sandpiper davası HHM için çok büyük olmaya başladı...
Howard's decided to partner with another firm.
Howard başka bir firmayla ortaklık kurmaya karar verdi.
Davis and Main. You heard of them?
Davis & Main. Hiç duydun mu?
- Sure, up in Santa Fe. - Right.
- Tabii Santa Fe'de. - Evet.
Well, they've heard of you, too, and they're interested.
Onlar da seni duymuşlar ve ilgileniyorlar.
They want to make you an offer contingent on an interview.
Sana bir toplantıyla teklifte bulunmak istiyorlar.
They've got a partner-track position in mind.
Akıllarında ortak rotalı bir pozisyon var.
Wait. What?
Dur biraz ne?
Partner track? What are you talking about?
Ortak rota mı? Neden bahsediyorsun?
I'm talking about there's an office in Santa Fe
Santa Fe'de bir ofis var diyorum...
with your name on it, or there could be,
...kapısında adın yazıyor, ya da yazabilir.
and you'd be working on your case.
Ve kendi dosyan üzerinde çalışacaksın.
I... well, I...
Yani ben...
I don't even, uh...
...ben hiç...
Chuck wouldn't like it.
Chuck bundan hoşlanmaz.
Chuck has no say in this.
Chuck'ın söz hakkı yok.
You wouldn't be working for HHM,
HHM'de çalışıyor olmayacaksın...
and Chuck can't tell Davis and Main who to hire.
...ve Chuck; Davis & Main'e kimi işe alacaklarını söyleyemez.
Why me?
Neden ben?
Is this like a tax write-off or a charity thing?
Bu vergi silme ya da hayır işi falan mı?
What's the angle, huh?
Amaç ne?
Jimmy, we've been talking to your clients,
Jimmy müvekkillerinle konuşuyoruz...
the sandpiper residents,
...Sandpiper sakinleri...
and they ask about you every chance they get.
...her fırsatını bulduklarında seni soruyorlar.
I don't know what it is, but you have a way with them.
Ne olduğunu bilmiyorum ama bir numaran var.
Hey. Old people love me.
Yaşlılar beni sever.
So... Sounds good?
Kulağa iyi geliyor mu?
Kim, I can't imagine what you did to make this happen.
Kim bunu gerçekleştirmek için ne yaptığını hayal edemiyorum.
Thank you.
Teşekkür ederim.
I didn't do anything... much.
Bir şey yapmadım... pek.
And believe it or not, Howard's been pushing this, too.
Ve inan ya da inanma Howard da bunu destekliyor.
Good, old Howard.
Ah şu Howard.
Listen, we're gonna be down in judge Murray's court
Dinle Perşembe 11'de yargıç Murray'nin...
on Thursday at 11:00.
...mahkemesinde olacağız.
The Davis and Main people will be there.
Davis & Main'dakiler de orda olacak.
It'd be the perfect chance for you to meet them.
Onlarla tanışman için müthiş bir şans olabilir.
Thursday at 11:00. All right, I'll be there.
Perşembe 11. Tamam orada olacağım.
Thanks, Kim, really.
Teşekkür ederim Kim, gerçekten.
I'll see you then.
Orda görüşürüz.
All the originals need to be copied and filed.
Tüm orijinal dosyalar kopyalanıp dosyalanmalı.
See, I've written right here on the box... "Copy and file."
Bak bu kutunun üzerinde "kopya dosyalar" yazdım.
That's to make it as clear as possible.
Olabildiğince açık olsun diye.
Got it, Mr. Mcgill. Anything else?
Anladım Bay Mcgill. Başka bir şey?
Well, on the grocery front,
Market alışverişi...
almost everything was right this time.
...düzgün sayılırdı bu sefer.
- Great. - Almost.
- Harika. - Sayılır.
Um, it's a small thing, but to my taste,
Küçük bir şey, ama bana göre...
the, uh, Granny Smith apples are a bit too tart.
...Granny Smith elmaları biraz fazla mayhoş.
- Those are the green ones, right? - Right.
- Yeşil olanlar değil mi? - Evet.
I prefer the red ones, but not red delicious.
Kırmızıları tercih ederim ama kırmızı tatlı yazanları değil...
Those are generally tasteless.
Onlar genelde lezzetsiz.
Fujis should be in season.
Fuji mevsimi olmalı.
It's not a major issue, but...
Çok mühim bir mesele değil ama...
- Yeah. - Fuji apples.
- Evet. - Fuji elmaları.
Okay.
Peki.
Oh, and I'd like to try soy milk,
Bir de soya sütü denemek istiyorum...
so maybe a half gallon of that.
...belki iki litre de ondan.
You got it.
Tamamdır.
Well, thank you, Ernesto.
Teşekkürler Ernesto.
I appreciate your attention to detail.
Detaya olan dikkatine minnettarım.
Do you need to write any of this down?
Bunların hiçbirini yazmak ister miydin?
'Cause it's okay if you do.
Çünkü istersen yazabilirsin.
You know, just to be sure.
Sadece emin olmak için.
So, Fuji apples.
Fuji elmaları.
Hey, Ernie.
Hey Ernie.
Hey. How you doing, man?
Nasıl gidiyor dostum?
Good, good.
İyi, iyi.
So, Howard's got you looking after Chuck, huh?
Howard, Chuck'la ilgilenmen için seni gönderdi demek?
Yeah. It's a few extra bucks, you know?
Evet birkaç kuruş fazla anlarsın ya?
How's he doing?
Durumu nasıl?
Seems okay, like usual.
İyi görünüyor, her zamanki gibi.
I'd say we could grab a beer,
Birer bira içelim derdim ama...
but they're waiting on all that paperwork back at the office...
...ofiste yazı işleri için bekliyorlar.
You know how it is.
Nasıldır bilirsin.
Don't I, though?
Bilmez miyim?
See you, Jimmy.
Görüşürüz Jimmy.
Uh, see you 'round, ernie.
Görüşürüz Ernie.
You done business with him before?
Onunla daha önce iş yapmış mıydın?
Right.
Tabii.
Yeah. I'll be there.
Evet. Orda olacağım.
Davis and Main and Mcgill.
Davis & Main & Mcgill.
Great to meet you.
Tanıştığımıza memnun oldum.
Nice to meet you, gentlemen.
Tanıştığımıza memnun oldum beyler.
It's good to meet you.
Sizi tandığıma sevindim.
Nice...
Tanış-
Well, that was quick.
Çabuk oldu.
- No charge. - Help me out here.
- Bakiye boş. - Yardımcı ol biraz.
Did I dream it, or did I have $1,600,000 on my desk in cash?
Rüya mı gördüm yoksa masamda 1.600.000 dolar nakit mi vardı?
When I close my eyes, I can still see it.
Hala gözlerimi kapattığımda onu görebiliyorum.
It's burned into my retinas like I was staring into the sun.
Güneşe bakmışım gibi retinalarıma kazınmış.
No one on God's green earth knew we had it.
Yer yüzünde hiç kimse bizim aldığımızı bilmiyordu.
We could have split it 50/50.
Yarı yarıya bölüşebilirdik.
We could have gone home with $800,000 each, tax-free.
Eve kişi başı 800.000 vergisiz dolarla dönebilirdik.
Your point being?
Demek istediğin?
Why didn't we? What stopped us?
Neden yapmadık? Bizi durduran neydi?
I remember you saying something about doing the right thing.
Doğru olanı yapmakla ilgili bir şeyler söylediğini hatırlıyorum.
I don't even know what that means.
Onun ne demek olduğunu bile bilmiyorum.
You want to know why I didn't take that money?
Parayı neden almadığımı bilmek mi istiyorsun?
Is that what you're asking?
Bunu mu soruyorsun?
Yeah, that's what I'm asking.
Evet bunu soruyorum.
Me, personally... I was hired to do a job.
Benim için şahsen, bir iş için tutulmuştum.
I did it. That's as far as it goes.
O işi yaptım. Olacağı oydu.
Yeah. Well, I know what stopped me.
Evet, ben beni neyin durdurduğunu biliyorum.
And you know what? It's never stopping me again.
Ve ne var biliyor musun? O beni bir daha durdurmayacak.
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk www.addic7ed.com
aylinergenc@gmail.com